Luzia Manuel

■ luzia21332@outlook.com



India, New Delhi



+91 9818316059



Luzia Manuel



LuziaManuel22



https://luziamanuel22.github.io/Luzia Portfolio/

About Me

I am a third year student at IIIT Delhi, majoring in Computer Science and Design. Currently, I am learning and working as an UI/UX Designer.

I am an avid reader and love listening to music. I am a constant learner who proactively seeks knowledge and opportunities to learn and grow.

Skills

- teamwork
- Creativity
- Active Listening
- Organization
- · Innovative thinking

Expertise

- UI/UX
- · Web Design
- Wireframes
- Storyboards
- Design Thinking
- Front End Coding
- UX Reserach
- · Research Methods
- User Research

Tools

Adobe Ilustrator

Adobe InDesign

Figma

Adobe Lightroom

Adobe Premiere Pro

HTML

CSS

Javascript

Canva

Language

Portuguese

English

Spanish



Education

Indraprastha Institute of Information Technology - Delhi, India

B. Tech - Computer Science and Design.

2021-Present

Relevant coursework: Data Structures and Algorithms, Algorithm Design, Operating Systems, DBMS, Computer Organization, and Human-Computer Interaction(UX/UI), Design Processes and Perspectives, Prototyping of Interactives Systems, Design of Interactives Systems, Visual Design And Communication.

Instituto Superior de Tecnologias de Informação e Comunicação, Angola

2018-2021

Electronic engineering and telecommunications

Instituto Medio Técnico Sao Benedito, Angola

2014-2016

High School - Computer Technician.

Received mention of merit for performances in the 10th and 11th grade.

Winner of the 12th grade Math Olympiad at school.

Project work

Course: (Design processes and perspectives) :Final Project

Course: (Visual Design and Communication): Mid Project

Course: (Design of Interactive Systems): **Portfolio**

Digital Solution for Efficient Waste Management: Project

Experiences

Woman Techmakers Luanda: Designer

April 2023- Present

Skills: UI/UX Designer, Video Editor, Photographer Editor

Accessibility and Inclusive Design: Undergraduate Researcher

January 2024- Present

Topic: Web accessibility for the elderly

Description: Develop heuristics, a sample webpage, user evaluations and writing a paper

Skills: Web Development, User Research, Research Methods, Design Thinking

Certifications/Technical Certificates

IT essentials : Cisco Network Academy

Fundamentals of User Experience (UX) Design: Google

Iniciar o processo de design de UX: criar empatia, definir e idealizar: Google

Construir wireframes e protótipos de baixa fidelidade: Google

FrontEnd Web Development: **BUKA**Figma for UX Design: **LinkedIn**Learning Anime.js: **LinkedIn**

Interests/Hobbies

Cook Photography
Music Handball